<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-01-06T16:35:18-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">TechLore Community Landing Page</title><subtitle>Sharing Tech's Tribal Knowledge</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Welcome to TechLore</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/welcome-techlore/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to TechLore" /><published>2018-01-05T14:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2018-01-05T14:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/welcome-techlore</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/welcome-techlore/">&lt;p&gt;Hey, Techlore community, Happy New Year!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After much deliberation, I have decided to shift this group from a book club to more of a community forum. After starting Techlore as a new years resolution in 2017, I found that although many members are interested in reading more and improving their awareness of tech’s effect on our communities through literature - not many have or make the time to actually read a book a month and contribute to the discussion sessions on a regular basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having the community add to a &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1LtdfV8Wdop13PvYOZrkL4EHEsGVJKxobob7Hc5RXKcQ/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;reading list&lt;/a&gt; and vote for a new book each month has allowed for a wider breadth of topics and books than I would have necessarily chosen myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personally, I do feel this group has created a stronger habit for me of reading and sharing the ideas and concepts I have learned in a public forum. I am very grateful to have had an opportunity to share this experience with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As of 2018, my new resolution is to start sharing my writing more consistently. SO, I will be choosing a relevant book to our community and will be sharing blog posts on the topics covered in the literature with thoughts on how it affects our community and our greater society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I encourage you to use this forum to share your own thoughts and ideas on empowerment, entrepreneurship, culture, social justice, and inclusion through the lens of technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Best,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lauranmontoya.com/&quot;&gt;Laura Montoya&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Laura Montoya</name></author><summary type="html">Hey, Techlore community, Happy New Year!</summary></entry></feed>